radarmagazine.com 2004-06-03

# Radar Magazine - Privacy policy

**  
PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE.**

As used herein, the phrase "this site" refers to [www.radarmagazine.com](http://www.radarmagazine.com/), which originates in the United States and is owned by Radar Media LLC (Radar). By using this site, you indicate your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, you should not remain on this site.

Radar reserves the right to change this Policy at any time. Your use of this site after any such notice is posted on this site means that you accept these changes.

Radar understands and respects your desire for privacy. To that end, we want you to know how we use the personal information you provide to us. 

We collect personally identifying information (such as your name and email address) when you register for our online newsletter or participate in other interactive online activities through this site. As described below, we may use such information to award prizes or, with your permission, for promotional and marketing purposes. We may also provide such information to reputable third-party companies so that they may keep you apprised of products and services that may be of interest to you, but only with your permission. 

We also collect non-personally-identifiable information (such as your IP address or domain, or about your site usage) for purposes of site administration and to compile aggregate information about usage of the site.

You will be asked for your credit card information if you subscribe to Radar Magazine or buy any other product from the site. Your credit card information is not collected or retained by Radar. It, along with the personal identifying information you submit, is transferred to and used by third-party vendors or service providers financial institutions to verify the credit card numbers and to authorize the processing of the transaction. Be sure to review all privacy policies published by our third-party providers and contact them directly if you have questions, as they may have privacy terms that differ from Radar's Privacy Policy.

Radar Online has implemented appropriate safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and to make proper use of the information that we collect. However, no transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed please be aware that to be completely secure. Thus, while we strive to protect your personal information, Radar cannot absolutely guarantee the security of any information you provide to us. 

To unsubscribe from the Radar Online newsletter and/or other electronic communications from Radar, enter your email address right here. You may also reply to the email newsletter with "UNSUBSCRIBE" (and only "UNSUBSCRIBE") in the subject line, or by following the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the e-mail. You can also unsubscribe from promotional and marketing emails that you receive from a Radar Online partner by typing "UNSUBSCRIBE" (and only "UNSUBSCRIBE") in the subject line in a reply to one of the partner's emails to you, or following the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the email. 

If you have any questions or concerns about the Radar Online Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact us at Radar Magazine, Privacy Policy, 41 East 11th Street, New York, NY 10003. 

**POLICY FOR USERS**  
Radar Online may collect personal information from users in order to provide them with a personalized online experience and to provide our advertisers a way to reach the right audience. Radar may share the personal and aggregate information we collect with our affiliates and other sites operated by and for Radar. On a confidential basis, Radar may also share personal information with our corporate affiliates or consultants or with third parties that perform a particular service on our behalf (such as fulfilling orders or for general site administration purposes). Radar shares aggregate information with third parties for advertising and promotional purposes. Radar may also disclose personal information in response to legal process, such as a request by law enforcement, a court order or subpoena, or to protect the integrity of our site if we believe that a guest has committed unlawful or otherwise harmful acts. 

With the permission of users, information submitted at the time of registration or submission may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by us and, also with the permission of the user, may be shared by us with companies that have agreed with Radar to use this information only for the marketing and promotion of its products and services. 

If guests elect to use our "E-mail to a Friend" referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask for the friend's e-mail address, and we will send an e-mail in response to your request inviting them to visit the site. This information is stored at Radar Online solely for the purpose of sending the e-mail.

**USE OF IP ADDRESSES**  
An Internet Protocol (IP) address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you log on to the Web. Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address, so when a guest requests pages from our site, our servers log the guest's IP address. The IP addresses of our guests are collected only for the purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers, our corporate affiliates or consultants, or with third parties that perform a particular service on our behalf. We do not combine IP addresses with any personally identifying information, nor do we compile any session activity reports by IP address.

**USE OF COOKIES**  
In cyberspace, cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes.

Cookies make Web surfing easier for you by saving your passwords, purchases, and preferences while you're at a site. The use of cookies is an industry standard; you'll find them at most major Web sites. 

By showing how and when guests use the site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not and help in targeting ads based on guest interests. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of guests and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. 

A cookie allows us to store the personal preferences that you set during each visit to our site, which in turn allows us to speed up your future activities at our site. Similarly, the stores hosted by our site usually use cookies to track which products you've chosen to purchase while shopping. Letting cookies do the record-keeping saves you the trouble of entering information over and over again. During future visits to our site, we will only read and retrieve information that we set in a cookie during an earlier visit to our site. 

The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is also standard in the Internet industry. Accordingly, you may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. Radar Online does not control these cookies, and they are not subject to the Radar Online Privacy Policy. By the same token, our advertisers do not have access to Radar Online's cookies. 

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of the site function properly if you do so. Specifically, you will not be able to purchase products or services through this site unless you accept a cookie. If you have any additional questions or concerns pertaining to the privacy of information collected on this site, send an email.

© 2003 Radar magazine. All rights reserved. RADAR Magazine is a registered trademark owned by Maer Roshan, and radar-mag.com and RadarMagazine.com are trademarks owned by Radar Media LLC.
